Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937-2012 UA.27.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accessions UA88-57, UA91-53, UA2008-0048, UA2008-0065, UA2012-0041, 6
  - Funny Business, Second City Improv with Fuqua Students -- (WNCN-17), 2000-03-16; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0043)
  - "Student Body", 93:53, 1994-05-16; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0044)
  - Founders' Day Convocation, 1996-12-12; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0045)
  - Durham County Library, Centennial Video, 1997; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0046)
  - Les Grands Duel Du Sport Basketball - Duke/North Carolina, by Antoine Roux, undated; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0048)
  - Happy Birthday! Judy Woodruff (Featuring Coach Mike Krzyzewski and president Nannerl O. Keohane, VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0049)
  - The Late Show with David Letterman with Coach Mike Krzyzewski; The Charlie Rose Show with Coach Mike Krzyzewski and Shane Battier, 2001-04-09; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0050)
  - Top Ten National Broadcast Stories, 1998, VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0051)
  - Good Morning America at Duke, November 1995, VHS; 2:03:13 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0052, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0017, Video-file UA27020001-VHS-0052.mov)
  - Dawson's Creek, Episode #501, "The Bostonians", 2001-10-10; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0053)
  - Inauguration of Nannerl O. Keohane, 1993-10-23; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0054)
  - The Charlie Rose Show featuring Coach Krzyzewsk, 2000-03-16; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0055)
  - Duke-Durham Neighborhood Partnership, NBC-17, 2005-01-12; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0056)
  - NC People, President Nannerl O. Keohane, 2004-02-06; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0057)
  - 20/20, 1993-01-29; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0058)
  - Good Morning America, 2002-04-29; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0059)
  - Shuttle V.N.R., 1994-04-04; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0060)
  - "The Charlie Rose Show" featuring Michael Hardt, 2001-07-24; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0061)
  - Alice Williamson Diary VNR, undated; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0062)
  - "Startemup.com," CNBC, 2000-05-03; VHS (Box 24, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0063)
  - Local News Compilation Tape, 1998-07/1999-02; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0064)
  - The David Letterman Show, Coach Krzyzewski, 2001-04-09; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0065)
  - Dawson's Creek, Episodes 1 and 2, Season 5, Duke highlights, 2001-10; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0066)
  - National Geographic, "K-ville", 2002-03-14; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0067)
  - Presidential News Conference, Keith Brodhead, WRAL, 2003-12-12; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0068)
  - The Charlie Rose Show, Katie Reefe, 03-29; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0069)
  - 1992-04-13 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0070)
  - The Late Show with David Letterman with Coach Mike Krzyzewski; The Charlie Rose Show with Coach Mike Krzyzewski and Shane Battier, 2001-04-09; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0071)
  - A Building Without Walls: The Levine Science Research Center, undated; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0072)
  - Keohane, Intro (#2), 1992 December; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0073)
  - Fox News, Whitehorn, 2003-01-27; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0074)
  - "Equal but Separate," 60 Minutes, 1993-04-25; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0075)
  - Orrin Pilkey, Beachfront Development/Erosion, undated; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0076)
  - Royal Blue: A Video History of Duke Basketball, 1992; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0077)
  - "The Life," Duke Basketball Profile, ESPN, 2002 March; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0078)
  - Online Education (includes Fuqua), 60 Minutes, 2001-02-18; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0079)
  - TV Coverage, 1998-07/1998-12; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0080)
  - TV Coverage, 1998-07/1998-12; VHS; 0:39:46 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0081, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0018, Video-file UA27020001-VHS-0081.mov)
  - Phytotron VNR, 1990 November; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0082)
  - 1999 National Broadcast Stories, VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0083)
  - "N.C. People," Nan Keohane (UNC-TV), 1993; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0084)
  - Peter and Virigina Nicholas Press Conference, 1995-12-07; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0085)
  - Professor Jim Cox, "News Hour/Lehrer," PBS, 2002-07-25; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0086)
  - Divinity School video, 1995; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0087)
  - Genomics Institute, WUNC-TV, 2000-12-04; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0088)
  - Nan Keohane's First Day, NBC Nightly News, 1993-08-12; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0089)
  - Good Morning America, 1992-09-16; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0090)
  - Living on the Edge: with the coastal risk assessment field guide, 1996; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0091)
  - 20/20 B72.3, 1989-06-05; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0092)
  - 1944 Historic Basketball Game: Duke vs. NCCU, 1997-04-01; VHS (Box 25, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0093)
  - "Outrageous Ambitions," halftime spot, basketball, 2002; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0094)
  - Y2K/Hospitals, PBS Newshour, 1999-08-05; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0095)
  - Rossiter retirement, undated; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0097)
  - "Business Dialogue," Time Warner Cable, 2004 January; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0098)
  - Duke Primate Center video by Jim Scarff, 1995; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0099)
  - Lobster Sound Release -- Sheila Patek, Duke University Graduate Student, 2001-05-09; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0100)
  - 60 Minutes, "Equal but Separate", 1993-04-25; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0101)
  - "Edge of Existence," Duke University Primate Center, undated; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0102)
  - Duke Online Sampler 2 -- Henry Petroski, African American Dance Ensemble, Dr. Dorie Reents, 1992-1993; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0103)
  - Richard Brodhead News Conference (introduction), Local TV Coverage, Tape 2 of 2, 2003-12-12; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0104)
  - Basketball/Academics, 2002-03-01; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0105)
  - Rachel Toor, "Admissions Confidential," NBC Today, 2001-08-27; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0106)
  - Genomics Institute, WUNC-TV, 2000-12-04; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0107)
  - Tom Wolfe speech, Duke Graduation, News 14 Carolina 1 p.m. Newscast, undated; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0108)
  - 1997 Top Ten National Broadcast Stories, VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0109)
  - 1999 National Broadcast Stories: Duke Medical Center, VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0110)
  - Ambitions Realized: A Nod to Nan, undated; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0111)
  - Duke-YMCA Story and Campus Security, NBC-17, WRAL, WTVD, 2004-04-02; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0112)
  - The Unveiling of the Plaque in Memory of Dr. Melvyn Lieberman, 1998-09-24; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0113)
  - Halftime Television Commercials -- Student Research and Student Life, 2003-11-13; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0114)
  - Kimberly Aiken Pag. Competition, 1985-1987; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0115)
  - Sticky Mittens, CNN, undated; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0116)
  - NC People, President Nannerl O. Keohane, 2004-02-06; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0117)
  - Duke News Service, News Master, 1999-01-20; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0118)
  - TV Coverage, 1998-07/1998-12; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0119)
  - TV Coverage, 1998-07/1998-12; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0120)
  - Nicholas Family Gift Announcement to Duke University, undated; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0121)
  - "Night of Duke Stars", 2001-08-16; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0122)
  - Ford Foundation Campus Diversity Initiative, 1998-10-06; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0123)
  - Education Summit, 2002-02-27; VHS (Box 26, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0124)
  - APPA Award for Excellence, Duke University Facilities Management Department, 2000 July; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0125)
  - APPA Award for Excellence, Duke University Facilities Management Department, 2000 July; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0126)
  - NC People, Richard Brodhead, 2005-05-13; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0127)
  - Summer 1998, VHS; 0:05:37 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0128, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0019, Video-file UA27020001-VHS-0128.mov)
  - Campaign for Duke Press Conference, 1998-10-01; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0129)
  - Inauguration of President Keohane, 1993-10-23; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0130)
  - The Charlie Rose Show featuring Coach Krzyzewsk, 2000-03-16; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0131)
  - The Late Show with David Letterman with Coach Mike Krzyzewski; The Charlie Rose Show with Coach Mike Krzyzewski and Shane Battier, 2001-04-09; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0132)
  - Duke News Service, News Master, 2000-11-15/2001-01-18; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0133)
  - Good Morning America, 2002-04-29; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0134)
  - Neurobics, WTVD-ABC, 1999-03-25; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0135)
  - John Hope Franklin and Duke Forest, undated; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0136)
  - "Hitler's Lost Plan," History Channel, 2004; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0137)
  - CBS 48 Hours, David Bailey, 2000-09-07; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0138)
  - Wal-Mart Frontline, Gary Gereffi Interview, 2004-08-20; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0139)
  - Local TV Inauguration Coverage, 1993-10-23; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0140)
  - 96 Highlights, Tape 2, undated; VHS; 1:30:50 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0141, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0020, Video-file UA27020001-VHS-0141.mov)
  - 2000 Duke Divinity School, VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0142)
  - CBS This Morning, 1988-12-06; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0143)
  - Duke Law School -- Rehnquist -- C-Span, 2002-04-13; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0144)
  - "Education Summit," Sanford Institution, UNC-TV, 2002 February; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0145)
  - Top Ten National Broadcast Stories, 1998, VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0146)
  - Duke/Arizona National Championship; NCAA Title Game, 2001-04-02; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0147)
  - Billion Dollar Babe, Version 2, 1998-01-28; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0148)
  - Duke News Service, News Master, 2000-10-18/2000-11-14; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0149)
  - Duke News Service, News Master, 2002-04-03; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0150)
  - Whitehorn/Speaker (Dean Bill Chafe), 2003-02-10; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0151)
  - "The Secret Life of the Mind," UNC-TV, 2002-01-22; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0152)
  - 60 Minutes (dub), 1993-04-25; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0153)
  - Duke News Service, News Master, 2000-09-08/2000-10-17; VHS (Box 27, Video-cassette UA27.02.0001-VHS-0154)
  - 2002 Boyarsky Lecture w/ Dr. Craig Venter Disc One, 2002-09-27; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0001)
  - 2002 Boyarsky Lecture w/ Dr. Craig Venter Disc Two, 2002-09-27; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0002)
  - Duke Commencement 2006 John Hope Franklin (Full Excerpts), Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0003)
  - Duke Commencement 2007 Rick Wagoner, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0004)
  - Duke Commencement 2008 Barbara Kingsolver, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0005)
  - Duke Commencement 2009 Oprah Winfrey, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0006)
  - Duke Commencement 2011 John Chambers, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0007)
  - Ariel Dorfman Desert Memories WUNC-FM 12-18-03 33 min., 2003-12-18; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0008)
  - NC Now 1/10/07 Charlie Soong 8 min., 2007-01-10; DVD; 0:08:13 (Box 28, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0059, Digital-materials UA27020001-SET-0005, Video-file UA27020001-DVD-0059.mp4)
  - Blue Mondays' Blues from Southgate Dorm, 2004-05 by Residents Friends of Southgate, Duke Univ., 2004-2005; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0010)
  - NC Now Digital Conference @ Duke UNC-TV 4/30/04 5 min. 20MB .avi, 2004-04-30; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0011)
  - DAA Reunions 4/06, 2006 April; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0012)
  - Nicholas School Radio Spots (3) :30 each Duke Radio Network Oct. 2007, 2007 October; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0013)
  - 9/11 5 Years Later 60 min. 9/11/06 NPR, 2006-09-11; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0014)
  - Young Artists uncompressed QT, undated; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0015)
  - Underwater Robot Prof. Jason Janet, Pratt School mpeg-4 Quicktime, undated; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0016)
  - Sound of Africa, undated; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0017)
  - DAA Homecoming #2, undated; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0018)
  - Milton at 400! (audio) Dec. 9, 2008 27 min. mp3, 2008-12-09; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0019)
  - "Monkeys Learn to Control Robot Limbs" NPR All Things Considered Oct. 13, 2003 3:40 .wav, 2003-10-13; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0020)
  - "The Digital Promise" w/ Prof. Cathy Davidson UNC-TV 4/30/04 .avi 5 min., 2004-04-30; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0021)
  - Prof. Richard Hays Divinity Sch. Ivey Address 1/28/03 57 min., 2003-01-28; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0022)
  - Audio excerpts from "You're the First One I've Told" New Faces of HIV in the South (Rutgers Press, 2002) Copyright 2002 Kathryn Whetten-Goldstein and Trang Quyen Nguyen, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0023)
  - iPod TV Clips August 2004, 2004 August; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0024)
  - Dukebasics 2003, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0025)
  - Brodhead, Krzyzewski, Alleva Press Conference, 2004-07-05; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0026)
  - The Connection from WBUR Boston and NPR Hour Two mono Tuesday January 14, 2003 Bird Brains, 2003-01-14; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0027)
  - Duke University Chapel #1 5/11/07 5pm Baccalaureate Service Tk 5-Sermon-Wells, Tk 7-President's Charge-Brodhead - copy -, 2007-05-11; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0028)
  - Duke Magazine journalism panels Oct. 20, 2006 .mov + .mp3 formats of each, 2006-10-20; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0029)
  - Convocation 2006 audio file Brodhead speech 8/22/06, 2006-08-22; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0030)
  - Brodhead Inauguration "Duke: Past, Present, Future" panel 9/18/04, 2004-09-18; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0031)
  - WUNC-FM "State of Things" Burness et al, 3/1/06 "Higher Ed and the NC Economy", 2006-03-01; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0032)
  - Primate Center 2005 Dean Gibson v.o., Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0033)
  - "Voices" CD master HIV/AIDS project Prof. Kate Whetten-Goldstein, undated; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0034)
  - Orangutans Prof. Carel Van Shaik Duke Univ. 2003, Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0035)
  - Tracy Futney Primetime 9/13/07, 2007-09-13; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0036)
  - Dr. Ralph Snyderman DUMC "NC Report" 30 m. 11/03, 2003 November; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0037)
  - Do No Harm A Radio Magazine on Medical Ethics (4 disc set), 2001; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0038)
  - Med Minute Audio 4/4/03-7/11/03, 2003-04-04/2003-07-11; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0039)
  - Med Minute Audio 7/03-9/03, 2003-07/2003-09; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0040)
  - Med Minute Audio 9/01-12/01, 2001-09/2001-12; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0041)
  - Med Minute Audio 9/03-12/03, 2003-09/2003-12; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0042)
  - Med Minute Audio 1/03-3/03, 2003-01/2003-03; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0043)
  - Med Minute Audio 4/01-7/01, 2001-04/2001-07; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0044)
  - Med Minute Audio 3/15/02-8/30/02 .wav files, 2002-03-15/2002-08-30; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0045)
  - Med Minute Audio 9/6/02-12/13/02 .wav, 2002-09-06/2002-12-13; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0046)
  - Med Minute Audio 01/02-05/02, 2002-01/2002-05; Compact disc (Box 28, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0047)
  - Music Matters (BBC Radio 3) inc. R. Larry Todd's discussion on Mendelssohn Sunday 1/4/04, 2004-01-04; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0048)
  - DAA Homecoming, undated; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0049)
  - Bob Edwards Show David Broder/Reynolds Price "The Good Priest's Son" 9/12/05 XM Satellite Radio, 2005-09-12; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0050)
  - Graduate Convocation Duke Chapel 8/19/04 4pm Track 7 - Convocation Address President Richard Brodhead introduced by Dean Lewis Siegel, 2004-08-19; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0051)
  - Graduate and Professional Students 2008 16 min "The Power of Their Presence" RealPlayer, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0052)
  - Prof. Kate Whetten-Goldstein Duke Univ. audio excerpts from "You're the First One I've Told" HIV/AIDS in the South copyright 2002, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0053)
  - Richardson's Roundup Bill Richardson in Conversation with Dr. Erich Jarvis, 3/3/03 CBC Radio One, 2003-03-03; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0054)
  - "Duke Today" radio 2008-2009 90 sec. ea. 21 programs, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0055)
  - "Duke Today" radio 2009-2010 90 sec. ea. 23 programs mp3, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0056)
  - "Duke Today" radio 2010-2011 19 programs mp3, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0057)
  - "Duke Today" radio 2011-2012 19 program 90 sec. eac. 19 programs mp3, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0058)
  - Hubert Humphrey Speech, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0059)
  - Richard Nixon Press Conference, Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0060)
  - Duke University Medical Center -- Jim Jaggers statement, 2003-02-22; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0061)
  - Duke University Graduation 2005, Disc 1, 2005-05-15; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0062)
  - Duke University Graduation 2005, Disc 2, 2005-05-15; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0063)
  - Inauguration Panel #3, "Global Challenges," President Brodhead Inauguration, 2004-09-18; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0064)
  - NPR "Hydraulic Fluid", 2005-08-12; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0065)
  - "Mark Twain," Professor Louis Budd, 2002-10-03; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0066)
  - "Conversation" Keohane/Rhodes, 2004-02-03; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0067)
  - Duke University Undergraduate Convocation 2004, Convocation Address and Tracts # 9 from President Richard Brodhead, 2004-08-14; Compact disc (Box 29)
  - Baccalaureate Service, TK6-Sermon-Wells; TK8-President's Charge-Brodhead, 2007-05-12; Compact disc (Box 29, Audio-cd UA27.02.0001-CD-0069)
  - Duke TV Spot 2003-2004 :30, DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0001)
  - Tom Wolfe (1 hr, 20 min) "Festival of the Book" 04/06, 2006 April; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0002)
  - Duke-NCSU "Green Game" 1/31/08 2 hrs, 2008-01-31; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0003)
  - Affording Opportunity Duke's Financial Aid Initiative Changing Lives Changing the World copyright 2006, DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0004)
  - Star Trek Tech Inv. Cloak, Brady Lab 2/19/07, 2007-02-19; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0005)
  - Duke-NCSU "Green Game" Report NBC-17 1/31/08 2 min., 2008-01-31; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0006)
  - HBO "Costas Now" 3/13/07 Coach K Profile 10 min., 2007-03-13; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0007)
  - Sarah Schroth's lecture 8/28/08 "Patronage and Style at the Court of Philip III", 2008-08-28; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0008)
  - Thank You, John! A Video Tribute to John Burness 5/13/08, 2008-05-13; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0009)
  - Thank You, John! A Video Tribute to John Burness 5/13/08, 2008-05-13; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0010)
  - Link Teaching and Learning Center, undated; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0011)
  - The Siamese Connection by Josh Gibson 76 mins 4:3 2008 NTSC, DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0012)
  - Duke On Camera CASE Entry 2007, DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0013)
  - A Salute to Jerry Black Facilities Management Dept., 9/03 TRT-8:15, 2003 September; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0014)
  - K Lab Video News Release 10/05, 2005 October; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0015)
  - Native Tales Plants Have Stories to Tell 4th Grade Activities NC Native Plants across the Curriculum, 2006; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0016)
  - Tracy Kidder and Paul Framer A Conversation 9/29/04 Page Aud., 2004-09-29; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0017)
  - In My Own Words Grant Hill 2/24/10, 2010-02-24; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0018)
  - The City Club of Cleveland Dr. Richard Brodhead photos 11/10/06, 2006-11-10; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0019)
  - Brodhead Speech "Student Life at Duke" w/ Q, 2005-03-22; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0020)
  - NC People 5/13/05 Pres. Brodhead, 2005-05-13; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0021)
  - PBS NOVA Science 10/18/05 w/ Erich Jarvis (full program), 2005-10-18; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0022)
  - 8 Bonds for a Better Durham, undated; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0023)
  - Nan Keohane Testimonial Data DVD 3/14/08, 2008-03-14; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0024)
  - Nasher Media Day Remarks by RHB 9/28, DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0025)
  - Prof. Alex Roland (History) C-Span 4/19/05 30 min. NASA, 2005-04-19; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0026)
  - MLK part 1 created 12/10/07, 2007-12-10; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0027)
  - MLK part 2 created 12/10/07, 2007-12-10; DVD (Box 29, Video-disc UA27.02.0001-DVD-0028)